This is the oppressed. This is the oppressor. This is the exploited. This is the exploiter.
And these people in this class have divided themselves. They say, I'm black, and I hate white people.
I'm hillbid. I hate Indians.
What up, family? So today is the anniversary of Fred Hampton's assassination.
The reason why I think it's important to put that in focus is because in this age where different groups across the United States are realizing that we have more in common than we have differences,
and that we are all being oppressed by the elites, we need to celebrate and remember the strategy that Fred Hampton used in uniting different groups.
Remember, he brought the Rednecks, the Puerto Ricans, and the black community together.
This was very significant for its time.
The fact that he was able to unite these three groups was a testament to the wisdom that is needed to reach out to groups in the working class.
I also want to say that as a white man, Fred Hampton means a lot to me because he reached out to poor whites.
He did not see the struggle of the black community separate from the struggle of the poor white community.
He saw the both as one, and that means a lot. It should mean a lot to poor whites.
Fred Hampton should be your hero because he looked past the oppression that the black community was going through.
He could have doubled down on some type of black nationalism and said, fuck all the other skin colors.
I'm just going to care about black people. No, he saw the suffering of poor whites who were being beat the shit out of by cops.
Hillbillies, as they were called as they were getting their asses whooped by the police officers because they were just deemed as trash.
The only reason why that momentum stopped and the only reason why that whole effort failed was because of the FBI and because of the U.S. government.
Because they knew that uniting different cultures, different formally opposing factions of races and ethnicities, ideologies within the United States was the biggest threat to the power of the elites.
So keep that in focus and study the tactics and wisdom that he used to bring these three groups together with the Rainbow Coalition.
And understand that all the government programs that the working class benefits from, WIC, SNAP, free healthcare clinics for communities, that was all started by the Black Panther Party.
Don't forget, the U.S. government did not willingly give us these services.
It was not out of the kindness of their hearts that they gave us these services.
It was because the Black Panthers were threatening their power by offering it to the people.
And the U.S. government took it, co-opted it, and packaged it up as some type of, you know, elite white man's invention for the people.
But it was in fact a platitude to prevent revolution from happening by people like the Black Panthers.
And for you white supremacists out there, understand that white supremacy is a fucking psyop designed to further enslave you.
There is no return on investment for white supremacy.
You are simply buying more time.
You will be the last on the menu, but you will be on the menu for the elites.
Mark my words, your children will be on the menu for the elites.
Now, if you want to help the Black Panther Party right now, get right back involved and get back to Fred Hampton's vision.
Let's do it.
Go to U8.net, check out the plan for revolution, and send an email to unitedsovereignty at proton.me if you want to get in contact with the Black Panther Party.
We are going to launch a full-scale revolutionary plan to the public on Colonial Outcast.
And I encourage you to watch it.
I'm not sure when exactly it's going to be.
We might air it Monday, but it's coming.
We're going to be having the Minister of Defense of the Black Panther Party on, the Minister of Education of the Black Panther Party on.
We are going to talk about the practical steps that we are all going to try to make for revolution.
It is a concise plan.
It's a step-by-step plan.
And we have an entire team to support you if you want to be involved in the Black Panther Party's efforts for this.
So please, be like a Fred Hampton.
Try to emulate Fred Hampton's wisdom in your daily life.
Try to be like him.
That's a very high bar.
But, in this age, we have no fucking choice.
As always, love you, fam.
The Deputy Chairman of the State of Illinois at the Black Panther Party is Fred Hampton.
And a lot of people don't understand the Black Panther Party's relationship with white mother country radicals.
A lot of people don't even understand that word that Eric uses a lot.
But what we're saying is that there are white people in the mother country that are for the same type of things that we are for stimulating revolution in the mother country.
And we said that we would work with anybody and form a coalition with anybody that has revolution on their mind.
We're not a racist organization because we understand that racism is an excuse used for capitalism.
And we know that racism is just a bi-product of capitalism.
Everything would be all right if everything was put back in the hands of the people.
And we're going to have to put it back in the hands of the people.
In the state of Illinois, it's going to have to be involved or even around the revolution because we're going to have one.
We're going to have to do more than talk.
We're going to have to do more than listen.
We're going to even have to do more than learn.
We're going to have to start practicing, and that's very hard.
We're going to have to start learning, and you learn through practice.
We're going to have to start making mistakes, and you learn through making mistakes.
We're going to have to start getting out there with the people.
And a lot of times we think we're better than the people, but that's an insult and that's criminal.
This is the oppressed. This is the oppressor.
This is the exploiting. This is the exploiter.
And these people in this class have divided themselves and said, I'm black and I hate white people.
I'm white and I hate black people.
I'm Latin American and I hate hillbillies.
I'm hillbillies, I hate Indians.
So we fight amongst each other.
And you've heard the testimony of pigs here.
You got pigs of all colors, you know that.
You got pigs that are white, you got pigs that are black, you even got pigs that are black and white.
Propagating the same type of madness that this buffoon Henry had would be propagating if he were here himself.
They want to keep you to believing that I'm your enemy and that everybody else that's black and that wears a lot of hair on his head and hair on his face, they want to keep you thinking that he's your enemy.
Because if ever you would disregard him and overlook him just for a minute and throw away that question of racism and started to deal with a little logic, then there would be no one else you can attack other than Henry Hand, other than David, and other than Tricky Dicky Mixon.